friendshangout.com 2011-11-24

# 3D Virtual Worlds & Chat Rooms - Create Your OWN Virtual World - Release 1.36

**Privacy Policy**   
FriendsHangout.com is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of those who use FriendsHangout.com. This statement outlines how we handle any personal information we obtain. 

From time to time, we may ask for information that personally identifies you, as in user surveys or orders placed through our site. We use this information to operate this site, provide you with the highest quality services and offer you opportunities we think will be of interest. 

You also may choose to provide personal information by participating in various forums we intend to offer for readers. You should remember that when you yourself voluntarily disclose personal information to other Internet users, such as when you include personal information in a posting to an online discussion forum, that information could be used by others and may result in unsolicited messages or other forms of attention. 

We use IP addresses to analyze traffic and administer this site. IP addresses track individual computers and do not contain personally identifiable data. 

In order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers and others, we may disclose user information, but only in a form that does not identify individual users. For example, we might disclose that a certain percentage of our users are from US households or within a certain age range. 

**Privacy of Minors**   
We are committed to comply with the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”). COPPA defines a "Child" as anyone under the age of 13. Children are not eligible to use the site unsupervised. If you are under the age of 13, you may only use this site in conjunction with and under the supervision of your parents or guardians. Internet safety experts have advised that children do not fully appreciate the risk of providing too much personal information online or communicating with strangers they encounter online. 

**Cookies**   
A "cookie" is a small data text file that can be placed in your browser to enable a server to recognize you each time you visit this site. Cookies may be placed on reader's computers from time to time by FriendsHangout.com or its advertisers. 

Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information. FriendsHangout.com does not use cookies to collect personal information. Instead, they may sometimes be used to track which parts of our site you have used so that we can better serve you when you return. Cookies may be used to provide you with information and special opportunities tailored to your interests. Our advertisers may use cookies to determine or control how many times you see their message or to customize the message you are presented. 

**Email**   
FriendsHangout.com will never give your email address to anyone else. We will only send you mail in response to your questions, as follow-up to your transactions, or as part of services you have signed-up for. 

**Third Party Ad Serving and Sites**   
FriendsHangout.com works with carefully chosen third parties to serve ads to this site. In the course of serving those advertisements, our advertisers might collect what is known as "Click Stream Data," which is anonymous and includes a web user's IP address, web pages viewed, date and time of access and responses by a web surfer to an advertisement delivered by us. If you would like more information about this practice, read our advertisers Privacy Statement. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

Some of our pages contain links to other sites that may have information practices different from ours. FriendsHangout.com has no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. You should consult the privacy notices of any site you choose to visit. 

**Disclosing Information to Others**   
FriendsHangout.com will only disclose personal information when required to do so by law or when we have explicit permission to do so.
